flickrmusic.com 2007-12-04

# Flickr Music - Unlimited Latest Music Free to Download

**  
Privacy Policy**

We will protect the privacy of all information you share with us. We will not disclose, sell or transfer any personal information to any third parties, except where required by law. 

**Personal information**  
when you request a product or service from us, you may provide personal information that we need to fulfill your request. This personal information could include your name, address, phone number, email address, or credit card information. Examples of when you might provide personal information include purchasing a product or service, or subscribing to an email newsletter. 

**Automatic (non-personal) information**  
we automatically collect and store the following non-personal information about your visit for internal statistical purposes. 

  * Name of domain from which you access the Internet; 
  * Date and time you access our site; 
  * Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site; 
  * Information you view while visiting our web site. 

**Cookies**  
our web site may use cookies to provide optional features. You do NOT have to accept cookies. The cookies contain non-personal information - usually a unique identifier for your visit. 

**Security**  
we protect your personal information by using appropriate security measures. For example, we use encryption when transmitting sensitive data such as credit card information. 

**Safe shopping**  
Shopping on our web site is safe. We use industry-standard technologies, such as SSL encryption, to ensure your safety and security. 

**Links to other web sites**  
our web site may contain links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other Web sites. 

**Notification of changes**  
Whenever we change this privacy policy in a material manner, we will post a notice on the home page of our web site for 30 days. 

**Questions and feedback**  
If you have any questions or feedback, [Contact us](mailto:support@flickrmusic.com)
